The Clover Kingdom.
In this place where magic is everything,
there lives a magicless boy named Asta.
This brave young hero devotes blood, sweat, and tears
to becoming the next Wizard King.
Though Asta's situation is practically unheard of,
there are others residing in this kingdom
who possess at least a tiny amount of mana,
yet can barely use spells at all.
They make up a very small minority,
living their lives in the shadows.
But, like everyone else,
they do their best to survive.
It's a dream.
Yes Huh.
This is a dream.
hätten dat base
laundering
負ける夢は colourful
So
何度も何度も
夢の前 bench
壁を越える火
何度も何度も
偃そう未来に繋げよう
七色の日常を進め
You shine like a diamond
These events took place just before the Eye of the Midnight Sun
attacked the royal capital.
The setting is a town that was neither rich nor poor, neither large nor small.
Just an ordinary place, located somewhere within the common realm.
No!
Try to be strong. It should heal up quickly.
Goodbye. See you later.
Another great meal. Thanks a lot, Dazu.
Of course.
It really is delicious. You're a wonderful cook. I'll give you that much.
Got that right.
Oh, dear. What a shame we were sitting here talking so long that my soup seems to have gotten cold.
Sorry, I'll go reheat it for you.
There's no need to walk all the way to the kitchen. It'll be much easier to warm it up with your magic.
Go on.
Okay. I'll need your flame magic, Mother, and I hope you won't mind lending me your spatial magic as well, dear.
Ah, thank you. That's much better. That catalyst magic of yours really does come in handy.
I wish I could borrow other people's magic to use for my own purposes. That's a valuable skill.
It certainly is. My, that's good.
Run away!
Mommy! Help us!
Help us!
Human scum.
Prepare to suffer the wrath of the elves. Vengeance will be ours.
Don't worry. I'll save you, I swear.
Please, get us out. And hurry or we'll die.
C'mon, Dasu.
It's too early for the sun to be rising.
Curse you, human.
Look at that. It's the captain of the Golden Dawn's magic.
Beautiful.
That must mean the kingdom is saved, right?
To be continued...
Read this.
The Devil's Servants?
It says some of the Magic Knights were recently suspected of communicating with a Devil and using forbidden spells.
The accused will soon face trial by the Magic Parliament.
That attack we suffered...
It looks like it was just one of many incidents that affected the entire Kingdom.
Rumor has it, the only reason they did all of those terrible things was because a powerful Devil assumed possession of their bodies.
Somehow.
What?
What? They were possessed?
A Devil?
Read this.
I'm asking each one of you to make sure your squads are as strong as you can.
We only have six months, but please do everything possible to raise their stages to one.
We must defeat Spade to protect the residents of Heart, as well as our own Kingdom.
Does this arrangement work for you?
How do you mean, sir?
As we established, the Magic Knights need to train for the next six months in order to be successful in their battle against the Devil.
Asta's still waiting to receive a sentence, but surely you can table that decision until after this is dealt with, yes?
I suppose I don't object.
What is the meaning of this?
Asta of the Black Bulls?
And that damned Narrow Woman?
They're servants of the Devil!
We can't let them roam free for six months!
As I explained before, what matters right now is that we cooperate with the Heart Kingdom and the Magic Knights.
It's crucial that we maintain a unified front in the face of that Devil and the Spade Kingdom.
Sir!
It's already decided.
Forgive me for saying so, Lord Domnazio, but I can't believe that you'd approve of this!
That's because I don't.
However, there are many complicated factors in play here.
More important things.
The only thing more important is executing the Devil who caused this mess!
There are multiple parties to blame for what the Eye of the Midnight Sun did to our kingdom!
But that Devil was at the root of it all!
They killed my nephew, sir!
Enough.
I'm sorry, sir, but we need to put these vicious criminals to death!
It's the only way for us to protect our people!
The magic bar limit is supposed to be—
Silence!
Right.
I'll take my leave.
The Wizard King has Lord Domnazio wrapped around his little finger.
We can't let the Devil's servants go unpunished for half a year.
That's insane.
The scales of justice have tipped into the darkness.
It's up to me to bring them back into the light.
For the sake of the Clover Kingdom.
Is that him?
Yes, I'm certain of it.
He hates the Devil more than anyone else in the magic parliament.
Then let's go.
Excuse me, sir?
Are you Cowboy, by chance?
Yes, my name is Cowboy.
I'm sorry, but do I know you?
No, we haven't had the pleasure.
We were hoping you could spare some time to talk.
Uh, actually, I'm a little busy right now.
I lost my family when the Eye of the Midnight Sun attacked our village.
And not just them.
Many lives were lost.
Everything burned down.
I'm sorry to hear that.
There are countless others in our kingdom who suffered terribly after what happened.
Yes, we're well aware.
And we also know that you endured the same pain.
You lost someone precious to you as well, didn't you?
How do you know that?
We're looking for revenge for all the victims.
And we're going to need your help to achieve it.
You want me to help?
What do you intend to do?
My intent, or ours rather, is to destroy the Devil's servants with our own hands.
The Devil's servants?
Are you serious?
I'll need to hear your plans in a bit more detail.
Of course.
Let's discuss.
In the wake of the Eye of the Midnight Sun's attack, Order was returning to the capital.
Wizard King Julius Novacrono was swamped with paperwork from the rebuilding effort.
Meanwhile, the Magic Knight squads each engaged in their own vigorous training regiments,
in preparation for their coming battles with the Spain Kingdom and the Devil.
Hurry up!
What's wrong?
Quit stalling and come at me!
It's nothing.
But a little water would be pretty good right now.
Why don't we take a break for a while?
But I'm not thirsty at all, though.
I say it's time for a water break.
And I'm royalty, so I'm right!
You're always bringing that up.
What does you being royalty have to do with anything either way?
I said I need a break, so I'm gonna take a break, okay?
Hmm.
If you're not thirsty, then don't come with me, idiot.
I'm not sure what she's getting so mad at me for.
Do you know?
Nope.
Ah, well, might as well work out then, huh?
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten, eleven!
Oh, hey, you guys.
Man, water sounds good right now.
Think you could pour me a glass?
No, pour it yourself.
You know I outrank you.
It's quieter than usual.
That's because everybody's been out there training, except for Henry.
And you, slacker.
I'm just taking a quick water break.
And what about you?
Were you off spying on your sister like you usually do?
What was that?
I mean, uh...
Since you asked, I had to help train this miscreant.
With that done, now I'm off to keep watch over my perfect angel.
Keeping watch, is that what you call it?
Man, I'm beat!
We could make a great combo spell with my spatial magic and his mirror magic.
But the timing's been crazy hard to nail down.
I have to cleanse the filth from my body before I see my angel.
I can't offend her senses by showing up drenched in sweat.
Sister Teresa doesn't come back from her trip till tonight.
There was some big meeting for all the sisters in the church.
So I guess Ghosh wants to go visit Marie before she gets home.
And apparently I'm the lucky one who gets to go with him.
Well, when the cat's away, right?
We'll be together again soon, Marie.
Hi, Ghosh.
Will you need some help washing your back?
And after that, you can help me wash my back as well.
How long can he keep doing that?
He's already been at it for a while.
He must be starting to get hungry.
I'm not a cook, but I know I can at least make a sandwich.
Heads up, Marie!
It's coming your way!
Got it!
Nice kick!
There.
That must be her.
Indeed.
Marie Adlai.
Daughter of a disgraced noble.
Her brother is a former criminal.
And she herself was possessed by a devil.
She caused grave harm to many innocent people in the attack.
We need to take care of this before the old hag from the church returns.
Agreed.
Pardon me.
Come with me, servant of the devil.
You brat.
Just what do you think you're trying to pull?
You are going to try and grab her.
We're not going to let anybody take our friend.
That's right.
Back off.
Damn kids.
Who are these people?
I'll go get help.
Sister Teresa, come quick.
She still hasn't come back from her trip.
Someone's trying to take Marie.
Who are you guys?
Leave them scared.
Remember the name.
We are the devil banishers.
Step back.
I won't let anyone lay their hands on these kids.
Snow magic.
Go snow cry.
Of course they would show up when this sister's out of town.
Four of them?
Snow magic.
There's one behind me.
Why didn't I sense any mana?
Nish!
Stop!
Get off!
Let me go!
Come on, baby!
Get me down right now!
Guys, stop it!
Hurry!
Leave me alone!
You won't be escaping again, servant of the devil.
Why do you think I'm a servant of the devil?
The scale is tilting to darkness.
We must push it toward the light.
Stop there, you monsters!
What are you planning to do with that girl?
Someone contact the magic knights now!
Let's go.
No, Marie.
Leave her alone.
Marie, no!
Wait, please!
Someone!
Help me, please!
Please, gosh!
Save me!
What's wrong?
I could have sworn I heard an angel calling out to me just now.
Oh, hearing things now?
I'm sure Marie must be just as anxious to see me again, too.
What's that in your hand?
Are you feeding the beast today?
It's obviously a sandwich!
If you want to bite, then quit being a jerk and just ask me!
I don't.
Hey, Finral.
Nap time is over.
Let's go.
Whatever.
It's like none of you even know what the word seniority means.
All right, Noelle, I guess we'll be back in a bit.
A bit's not enough.
We'll be a while.
Well, then guess I'm going to be catching it from Yami in a while.
Here.
Okay, here we go.
81, 82, 22!
81, 82, 23!
81, 82, 24!
81, 82, 25!
81, 82, 26!
How long do you plan to be out here?
Until I get to 10,000!
81...
82...
Wait, no.
You distracted me with your quest!
That's all in lost count!
Now I have to start over from the beginning or I'll cut the workout short!
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7...
That must be Asta.
Yes, a boy with no mana and no magical ability.
And yet somehow he's managed to become a magic knight.
He's nothing but a filthy devil's servant.
Now then, let's do it.
All according to plan.
131, 132, 133, 134, 135, 136.
What? Is she alone?
Hang on!
Stay with me. What happened?
Please, take this.
What is this?
That was impressive. You're quite a skilled potion maker.
Thank you.
I had only counted on capturing the Devil's Servant, but it seems we found the Forbidden Magic Girl as well.
We truly must have luck on our side today.
So this is narrow.
Well, look at those horns. She's clearly a devil.
Indeed. They're proof that she used forbidden magic.
Now then, let's get them secured.
Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow!
Ow!
Let go!
How can we be that strong?
Can't stay conscious.
Narrow, let her go.
Please help me, Asta.
What do you people think you're doing?
Get away from Asta and Narrow right now!
Sealing magic.
Inverse release.
I can't move my body.
Oh, crap.
Am I gonna...
We're out of time. Let's go.
Water creation magic.
Seedragon...
Salt magic!
The flower on the road's done!
Water!
Sand magic.
Sand screen!
Now run!
Come back!
What was that?
There's something happening outside.
Asta!
Nero!
She's fast!
Water creation magic!
Seedragon's water bomb!
Oh!
Oh, crap!
There's no choice. Leave him.
I agree.
Please, forgive me.
Transparency magic.
Share the same fate.
Don't you dare leave without telling me who you are!
We are the devil banishers.
We will drive the devil to its demise.
You won't get away!
Not until Nero is safe!
I can't sense their mana.
Nero.
Asta!
How could anybody do that to little children?
What is all this?
Ghosh!
They took Marie!
You have to help her!
Asta, please wake up!
ASTA!
ー 作次第2 bestPacir punto
good movie
エンディング
ソフト
bilga Bagto
Francisco
клиmata
4 作詞 yep
IDsV
裸でに転んで
傷ついて
気づけば
It's such a sad kind
All sama nits
So you've been waiting for people
If we have a dream event
So long after I put down the badness but not to be like that of the days Iepherds
of thisем athlete I wasn't going to scare people
because I've needed for whatever time they请
I can't wait for it's fake thoughts
until I reach the way the help
you see things you can bring most of you
because we all hurt like she has broken
I've beenливо-hungadu
You can't die, Asta! Wake up! Make one of your dumb faces and laugh that stupid laugh of yours!
Black Clover, page 143, the tilted scale. They took Nero and Marie. What is it they're after?
Black Clover, page 143, the tilted scale.